

SHARWIN N SURESH KUMAR

NILAI UNIVERSITRY STUDENT

012 - 295 9879



sharwinsk@gmail.com



SharwinSK



🛖 71450 Seremban, Negeri Sembilan

Education

Jan 2023 - Present

Diploma In Computer Science Nilai University

Certificate Mechanical In **Engineering**

COLLEGE TAFE SEREMBAN Jan 2021 - Oct 2022

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia

SMK Seremban Jaya 2 2012-2016

Skills

Java

C ++

VB.net

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

MySql, PHP

CISCO

AutoCAD

Autodesk Inventor

Language

English

Malay

About me

As a Computer Science Student I has works hard and has a lot of experience making software also has leadership and problem-solving skills. I have ability in computer language such as Java and C++ and has worked with Automation and technical design before. Currently I am developing CMS System for the Nilai University.

Experience

President

2022 - Present

TADIKA ANAK BESTARI RAING RIA SEREMBAN

- Participated in Stategic Planing Session to ensure the Organization long term success.
- Develop a Quiz Game Application for kids using Vb.net

INTERN

ENGE PLAS AUTOMATION

Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

- Design Zeppelins Two Way Diverter, 360 Branch Diverter and Pneumatic Actuator.
- Machine Servicers and Quality Check Machine parts.
- Find Solution for Zenmark Shredder Machine overheat problem.
- Design Discharge Station Platform

Reference

Mr Lee Mr Izrulfizal Mr Rajendran

College TAFE / HOD ENGE PLAS/ Supervisor **NU Intership Coordinartor**

017 - 673 1628 017 - 474 1077 016 - 319 0969